hotelbeds.com 2006-06-21

# Hotelbeds Accommodation and Destination Services

About us

HOTELBEDS.com is a product of HOTELBEDS, a legally-constituted Spanish company registered in Palma de Mallorca with fiscal identification number B-28916765, based at Calle Benito Pérez Galdós, 34, Palma de Mallorca 07006, Baleares, Spain.  
HOTELBEDS is part of First Choice Holidays PLC.

HOTELBEDS offers the contracting of accommodation services in hotels, apartments or other establishments, transfers, excursions and other destination services subject to established contract conditions and general conditions stated on this web and according to prices and cancellation conditions displayed when making each reservation.

This legal statement and privacy policy are an integral part of HOTELBEDS website, which cannot be separated from the general contracting conditions, operations or reservations.

The use of this website indicates complete acceptance, without exclusion, of the conditions contained in these clauses.

Use of site.

The website will inform the user about the procedure for making reservations.

Access to HOTELBEDS may involve the use of cookies, although the website can run without them. Cookies are small files of information stored on the browser of each user so that the server can recognise certain information that only the server can read. Cookies last for a limited time. Cookies cannot extract any information from the user's hard drive or steal personal information.

Although cookies help HOTELBEDS system to optimise the booking process, users who do not wish to receive cookies or wish to be informed of their presence, can configure their browser to that effect.

Personal Data Protection.

HOTELBEDS may need to collect personal data and other information about consumers to deal with their booking. This information may include such details as client name, personal preferences, disabilities, or any special dietary or religious requirements. 

In complying with European Directives 95/46 and 2002/58, along with the rules that complement them, developed in accordance with the legislation of each country or any such rules that replace them (referred to from this point on as PDPR, Personal Data Protection Regulation) HOTELBEDS guarantees the security and confidentiality of any personal details submitted.

HOTELBEDS has implemented technical security measures and appropriate processes to ensure the correct transmission of personal data obtained for the purpose for which they have been submitted, as well as to ensure against unauthorised alteration, loss, treatment or access, in line with current technology and the nature of the data.

HOTELBEDS may disclose client's information to third parties only for the purpose of completing consumer's reservation and for the purposes of associated administration.  
Any data thus collected on this website may be transmitted, according to PDPR, to those entities that must be involved in order to contract the requested services.

Where client's stay is outside the European Economic Area (EEA), controls on data protection may not be as strong as the legal requirements in PDPR. HOTELBEDS will not however, pass any information on to any person not directly responsible for travel arrangements. 

If the owner of personal information held by HOTELBEDS would like at any time to exercise the right to access, correct, update or delete their personal information according to PDPR, please contact HOTELBEDS.

Coordinator LOPD Grupo Hotelbeds  
C/ Benito Pérez Galdós, 34  
E-07006 Palma de Mallorca  
Baleares / Spain  

Copyright

All materials and content on this site, including, but not limited to, software, logos, trademarks, graphics, text, designs, compilations of data, hotel reports, photographs, images, maps, and other material on this site are the intellectual property of HOTELBEDS or its suppliers and are protected by international copyright law. 

The web user is granted a limited, non-exclusive, non transferable, revocable licence to view these materials. The web user may not copy, reproduce, store, transmit, distribute, borrow, cache, modify, sell, make derivative works, or otherwise use the information without the express written consent of HOTELBEDS. 

Any violation, including through robots, spiders or other automated or manual means, may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. 

The information on this site is posted in good faith, but HOTELBEDS cannot guarantee that it is completely free from inaccuracies and typographical errors and does not accept liability for any error or omission on this site

IPR (Intellectual Property Rigths) in the photographs

HOTELBEDS wishes to thank the following institutions for the granted licence to use the photographs shown in this web site.
